myipaddress.com 2014-06-30

# myIPaddress.com: Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all personal information collected on this site. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information  
**Personal information is collected when you complete a form on this web site or when you visit pages on this web site. Your personal information is used to provide the services you request and to enhance this web site.

At times other companies may be hired to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings. We will only provide those companies with the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

We may share the information we collect with other companies. You may tell us not to share information about you by submitting a contact form and requesting that your information not be shared. Your choice will not affect sharing with companies performing marketing or other services for us, government entities in response to subpoenas or regulatory requirements, or as otherwise permitted by law.

**Use of Cookies**  
This web site may use a feature of your Internet browser called a cookie. This web site may use cookies to facilitate your Internet sessions, to maintain security, and to improve this web site. If you choose not to enable cookies on your browser, you will not be able to use some of the services offered on this web site.

**Children**  
The web site is not directed to children under age 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under age 13.

**To Further Protect Your Privacy**  
While exploring this web site, please be aware that third-party Internet sites and third-party services accessible through this web site have separate privacy and data collection policies and practices. These policies and practices are independent of and may be different from the policies and practices for this web site. We are not responsible or liable for these independent policies and practices and it is your responsibility to review them and decide whether or not they satisfactorily protect your rights.

**Changes to This Policy**  
This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 10, 2006 and replaces any previous Privacy Policy for this site. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time, and when such a change is made we will post a revised version on this web site. Changes will be effective when they are posted. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy from time to time to be aware of any such changes. Your continued use of the web site indicates your agreement to any such changes.
